<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Random Tech Stuff</title>
    <link>https://fsteffenhagen.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Random Tech Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 02:50:19 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fsteffenhagen.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://fsteffenhagen.github.io/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 02:50:19 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fsteffenhagen.github.io/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Felix Steffenhagen and I welcome you to my little web space. I&amp;rsquo;m interested in a lot of things but unfortunately there&amp;rsquo;s too little time to follow everything.
Mostly I&amp;rsquo;m interested in everything around Linux, Python, Coding, Software Engineering, command-line tools, Data Science, Photography, Reading, Playing Musical Instruments, Watches, Retro Games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://fsteffenhagen.github.io/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 02:34:55 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fsteffenhagen.github.io/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description> Tech and tools I use mostly OS  Ubuntu Linux  Programming Languages  awk Bash Golang Python  Web  Firefox: My default Browser Hugo: Static Site Generator  Command-line Tools  jq mtr tmux mycli  Coding tools  git PyCharm  Misc Tools  keepassx: Password Management  Websites I browse daily/weekly  https://blog.fefe.de https://news.ycombinator.com  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Txt</title>
      <link>https://fsteffenhagen.github.io/blog/did-txt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 01:01:18 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fsteffenhagen.github.io/blog/did-txt/</guid>
      <description>did.txt: Generate a minimalist micro journal using vim With all the distractions I&amp;rsquo;m facing in the office I sometimes find it hard to keep track of what I was doing. Some troubleshooting here, a bit of coding there, meetings, etc. Some days are just context switching from one task to the next. At the end of the day it&amp;rsquo;s still nice to turn back and track your progress and to have a reference point to start off next day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>